{
  "quizTitle": "Makanan Indonesia",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "🐌",
      "answer": "tutut",
      "hint": "T _ T _ T"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥔🌀",
      "answer": "kentang spiral",
      "hint": "K _ _ T _ _ G   S _ I _ _ L"
    },
    {
      "question": "🧱🏟️",
      "answer": "batagor",
      "hint": "_ A _ A _ O _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🌽🍼🧀",
      "answer": "jasuke",
      "hint": "J _ _ _ K _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍌🍳",
      "answer": "pisang goreng",
      "hint": "P _ _ _ _ G   G _ R _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍚🟡",
      "answer": "nasi kuning",
      "hint": "N A _ I   K _ N _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥩🥥🌶️",
      "answer": "rendang",
      "hint": "R _ N _ _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍚🐱",
      "answer": "nasi kucing",
      "hint": "N A _ I   K _ _ _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥭🥒🍍🍎",
      "answer": "rujak",
      "hint": "R _ _ _ K"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥜🥗",
      "answer": "gado-gado",
      "hint": "G _ _ _ - G _ _ _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍢",
      "answer": "sate",
      "hint": "S _ _ E"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍲🥩🍚",
      "answer": "rawon",
      "hint": "R _ _ _ N"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥟🌽",
      "answer": "perkedel jagung",
      "hint": "P _ _ _ _ _ _   J _ _ _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🐉🕺🏻",
      "answer": "nagasari",
      "hint": "N _ G _ S _ R _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍰❤️✌️",
      "answer": "kue lapis",
      "hint": "K _ _   L _ _ _ S"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍞💔",
      "answer": "roti sobek",
      "hint": "R _ _ I   S _ B E _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🐓🔨",
      "answer": "ayam geprek",
      "hint": "A _ _ M   G _ P _ _ K"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍗🌶️🍛",
      "answer": "ayam penyet",
      "hint": "A _ _ _   P _ _ _ _ T"
    },
    {
      "question": "🧠🧠",
      "answer": "otak otak",
      "hint": "O _ _ K   O _ _ K"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍜🐓",
      "answer": "mie ayam",
      "hint": "M _ _   A _ _ _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍚🏜️",
      "answer": "nasi padang",
      "hint": "N _ _ _   P _ _ _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥘🐐",
      "answer": "sop kambing",
      "hint": "S _ P   K _ M _ _ _ G"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍞🔥",
      "answer": "roti bakar",
      "hint": "R _ _ _   B _ _ _ R"
    },
    {
      "question": "🍚🧎",
      "answer": "nasi uduk",
      "hint": "N _ _ _   U _ _ _"
    },
    {
      "question": "🥣🍗",
      "answer": "bubur ayam",
      "hint": "B _ B U _  A _ A M"
    }
  ]
}
